[{"answer": "LUMENTHAL: I think that the issue remains a very open -- one in the minds of many of my colleagues because they are hearing from their constituents that we really need to do something about gun violence.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Are they going to do that?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well, the NRA never misses an opportunity to miss an opportunity.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Where does that leave the president?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "And what did you agree with him about?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "In French, back to the Bill of Rights.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "You don't agree with universal background checks for gun sales?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Infringe on my rights.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "You don't agree with that?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Well, here's the deal.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "What possible infringement of your rights is it as a member of the American society if you want to buy a gun that are background checked?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Would you cap ammunition magazines to a 10-round limit?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Because it doesn't say so in the Constitution.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Piers, more importantly where does it say I cannot?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, there is not because it doesn't say it.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "So where's the limit?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "You know what, honestly, I don't see bullet points in the Constitution, sure.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Do you believe the Second Amendment gives you, Scottie Hughes, the right to have a tank?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "That's an interesting question, Piers.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Do you feel you have the right to have a tank?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "No -- listen, listen, listen, listen -- no, listen.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "How can this be a sensible conversation?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "I haven't even said anything yet.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "-- say you want the right to a tank?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I think the Constitution is clear and it says that we have a right to bear arms under the definition of arms.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Do you think you should have the right to have a tank under the Second Amendment?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "If that is how arms is defined, I'm going to let you draw your conclusions on that.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Does that include a tank?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Dana, Dana, Dana -- I'll come to that in a moment.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "So have you started using the term -- have you stopped using the term assault rifle?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I believe that the Second Amendment gives us all the right to bear arms.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "The Second Amendment gives you, as Scottie believes, the right to have a tank?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "If that's how -- if it falls under the definition of firearms.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Does that include a tank?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "I -- if it falls under the definition of firearms.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Do you think it does?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "If I say so, you're going to -- you're going to fire back.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Do you think it does, Dana?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "And accuse me about my interpretation.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you think it does?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "My personal interpretation of the Second Amendment isn't a personal interpretation.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Does the -- does your personal interpretation of the Second Amendment include your right to have a tank?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "If it falls under the definition of firearms, Piers.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Does that include a tank?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Scottie has --", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "When is the last time you heard somebody want a tank and buy a tank?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, my brother is, yes.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "So you're an expert?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "And Columbine happened, and Columbine happened after that.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "You don't dispute that?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "And Columbine happened after that.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Do you dispute that it was banned?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Because people don't like scary-looking guns.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Why was it banned then under the 1994 assault weapons ban?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "OK, Dana Loesch, let's ask you that question which is about the magazine clips.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "When is the last time you heard a crime done by one of those people?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I think that there exist reasons that exactly why we should have more than.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Do you think that there is any reason why any civilian needs a magazine -- or magazine drums at it is now, over 10-round limit or more?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "And also, and also, Piers --", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "What is the point of that anecdote?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Well, because it's to highlight that if someone has a firearm and they're able to defend themselves --", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "But Dana, why do you tell that story?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Or -- I've seen -- I actually have screen shots of it.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Have you seen the video?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I'm not saying that.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "So that young man should have shot those people?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "There are instances where there is more than one people, more than one person coming at you.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "What are you saying then?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I haven't fired one.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Have you ever fired one?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Well, first and foremost, if you've never fired an AR- 15, as a woman, who also has self-defense -- has -- uses guns for self-defense and likes to know that I have that security they're a lot easier to fire than other rifles simply because of the recoil.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Why would anybody need that?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Piers, how are law-abiding --", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Or one of these high-capacity magazines?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "James Holmes was a law-abiding citizen.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Why should I be punished?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Scottie said early that she --", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Do you realize that there are laws that have been passed to incentivize states recording these people?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "You know, I'm really -- because I think that he was moved by what happened at Newtown, which I think anybody would have been.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Is there anything there you agreed with?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Was there anything you agreed within the president's proposals?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "-- I would have liked to have the mother from Georgia that sat there.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "You know something?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Well, he has this stuff he chose precisely because he doesn't have to send it through the Senate or the House.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "How can he do it?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I grew up on a farm in a world surrounded by guns.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Well, what the bloody hell are they?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Well, it's fun.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "What are you left with?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Is fun a good enough excuse?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "We know very little about this.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "We know that three Americans may be among the hostages, I think?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "How are you doing?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "I'm feeling great.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Thank you How are you?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think this is a really polarizing issue.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "What is your take on what was a very momentous day today for President Obama and his administration, and I think for America?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "Well, I think the Constitution -- when the Founding Fathers wrote the Constitution, I don't think they envisioned, you know, rapid-fire weapons or anything like that.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Do you believe the Constitution gives you the right to have a tank?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "But those are just two people.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "They couldn't find any common ground in anything?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "He basically, you know, asked me what the weather was going to be, and then kept moving.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "Did you get to know him?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "Well, look --", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "What do you think of it?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "I think, look, we were always energized.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "Do you feel like it's got you all energized again?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "Right, 205.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 851, "question": "Your neck is disappearing, like the rest of you, at a rate -- you've lost an unfeasible amount of wait, 350 pounds down to -- fighting wait now?", "qSentId": 850}, {"answer": "A, in this country, we need to cut back on portions.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 878, "question": "Because you can have all the diets and things in the world, but until your head's right -- what are the things that you felt were most effective?", "qSentId": 877}, {"answer": "Let me tell you about a high work out.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 906, "question": "Have you ever seen a happy runner?", "qSentId": 905}, {"answer": "I am sure there is worse, but here is the deal.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 922, "question": "The White House incident, probably the most revolting story I've ever heard on national television?", "qSentId": 921}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 943, "question": "Can we have you read the tease to the break, please?", "qSentId": 942}, {"answer": "It's going to be spectacular.", "docId": "130116pmt", "aSentId": 954, "question": "In one word, what will the weather be like tomorrow?", "qSentId": 953}]